BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XVIII: Code #61, Educational Services
  - Code no.811835: Waterbury Board of Education and National Education Association, 1989-1996 (Box 182, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Waterbury Board of Education and Waterbury Teachers Association, Connecticut Education Association, National Education Association, 1989-1992; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 182, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1989 and expires on 6/30/1992. Covers 1100 workers in Waterbury, CT
    - Item 2: Waterbury Board of Education and Waterbury Teachers Association, Connecticut Education Association, National Education Association, 1989-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 182, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1989 and expires on 6/30/1993. Covers 1100 workers in Waterbury, CT
    - Item 3: Waterbury Board of Education and Waterbury Teachers Association, Connecticut Education Association, National Education Association, 1992-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 182, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1992 and expires on 6/30/1993. Covers an unknown number of workers in Waterbury, CT
    - Item 4: Waterbury Board of Education and Waterbury Teachers Association, Connecticut Education Association, National Education Association, 1994-1996; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 182, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1994 and expires on 6/30/1996. Covers an unknown number of workers in Waterbury, CT
  - Code no.811857: Moreno Valley Unified School District and California Teachers Association, 1988-1996 (Box 182, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Moreno Valley Board of Education and Associated Teachers of Metropolitan Riverside, California Teachers Association, National Education Association, 1988-1991; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 182, Folder 20)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1988 and expires on 8/31/1991. Covers 1200 workers in Moreno Valley, CA
    - Item 2: Moreno Valley Unified School District and Associated Teachers of Metropolitan Riverside, Moreno Valley Caucus, California Teachers Association, National Education Association, 1990-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 182, Folder 20)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1990 and expires on 6/30/1993. Covers an unknown number of workers in Moreno Valley, CA
    - Item 3: Moreno Valley Board of Education and Moreno Valley Educators Association, California Teachers Association, National Education Association, 1991-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 182, Folder 20)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1991 and expires on 6/30/1993. Covers 1200 workers in Moreno Valley, CA
    - Item 4: Moreno Valley Board of Education and Moreno Valley Educators Association, California Teachers Association, National Education Association, 1993-1996; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 182, Folder 20)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1993 and expires on 6/30/1996. Covers 1200 workers in Moreno Valley, CA
  - Code no.811858: Orange United School District and CSEA, 1988-1991 (Box 182, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Orange Unified School District and California School Employees Association, Chapter 67, 1988-1991; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 182, Folder 21)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1988 and expires on 9/30/1991. Covers 1100 workers in Orange Co., CA
  - Code no.811859: Orange Unified School District and Orange Unified Employees Association, 1989-1992 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Orange Unified School District and Orange Unified Education Association, California Teachers Association, National Education Association, 1989-1992; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1989 and expires on 6/30/1992. Covers 1200 workers in Orange Co., CA
  - Code no.820363: New York City School District and United Federation of Teachers, 1973-1984 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Code no.811870: Flint Community Schools and United Teachers Association, 1992-2000 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: City of Flint Board of Education and United Teachers of Flint, Inc., 1992-1995; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1992 and expires on 8/31/1995. Covers an unknown number of workers in Flint, MI
    - Item 2: City of Flint Board of Education and United Teachers of Flint, Inc., 1995-2000; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1995 and expires on 8/31/2000. Covers an unknown number of workers in Flint, MI
  - Code no.811871: New Bedford Educators, Inc. and New Bedford Educators Association, 1992-1994 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: New Bedford School Committee and New Bedford Educators Association, Inc., 1992-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1992 and expires on 6/30/1994. Covers 1200 workers in New Bedford, MA
  - Code no.811877: Tucson Unified School District and Tucson Employees Association, 1993-2001 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Tucson Unified School District and Tucson Education Association, 1993-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1993 and expires on 6/30/1994. Covers 3200 workers in Tucson, AZ
    - Item 2: Tucson Unified School District and Tucson Education Association, 1996-1998; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1996 and expires on 6/30/1998. Covers an unknown number of workers in Tucson, AZ
    - Item 3: Tucson Unified School District and Tucson Education Association, 1998-1999; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1998 and expires on 6/30/1999. Covers an unknown number of workers in Tucson, AZ
    - Item 4: Tucson Unified School District and Tucson Education Association, 1999-2001; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1999 and expires on 6/30/2001. Covers 3200 workers in Tucson, AZ
  - Code no.820150: Illinois, University of and Service Employees International Union, 1995-2002 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: University of Illinois Board of Trustees and Service Employees Union, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 119, 1995-1998; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 8/27/1995 and expires on 8/22/1998. Covers 1100 workers in Urbana-Champaign, IL
    - Item 2: University of Illinois Board of Trustees and Service Employees Union, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Chapter 119, Local 73, 1998-2002; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 8/23/1998 and expires on 8/31/2002. Covers 1100 workers in Urbana-Champaign, IL
  - Code no.820785: Hamilton County Board of Education and Hamilton County Employees Association, 1981-1991 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Hamilton County Board of Education and Hamilton County Education Association, 1981-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 5/20/1981 and expires on 6/30/1982. Covers an unknown number of workers in Hamilton Co., TN
    - Item 2: Hamilton County Board of Education and Hamilton County Education Association, 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1982 and expires on 6/30/1985. Covers 1100 workers in Hamilton Co., TN
    - Item 3: Hamilton County Board of Education and Hamilton County Education Association, 1985-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1985 and expires on 6/30/1986. Covers 1100 workers in Hamilton Co., TN
    - Item 4: Hamilton County Board of Education and Hamilton County Education Association, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1986 and expires on 6/30/1989. Covers 1100 workers in Hamilton Co., TN
    - Item 5: Hamilton County Board of Education and Hamilton County Education Association, 1988-1991; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1988 and expires on 6/30/1991. Covers an unknown number of workers in Hamilton Co., TN
  - Code no.820812: Broward County School District and Florida Professional Employees, 1982-1994 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Broward County School Board and Broward Educational Office Personnel Association, 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1982 and expires on 6/30/1985. Covers 1000 workers in Broward Co., FL
    - Item 2: Broward County School Board and Federation of Public Employees, 1988-1991; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1988 and expires on 6/30/1991. Covers 1000 workers in Broward Co., FL
    - Item 3: Broward County School Board and Federation of Public Employees, 1991-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1991 and expires on 6/30/1994. Covers 1150 workers in Broward Co., FL
  - Code no.820829: Okaloosa County School Board and Okaloosa County Employees Association, 1991-2000 (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Okaloosa County School Board and Okaloosa County Education Association, 1991-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 8/14/1991 and expires on 8/14/1994. Covers 1700 workers in Okaloosa Co., FL
    - Item 2: Okaloosa County School Board and Okaloosa County Education Association, 1994-1997; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 8/14/1994 and expires on 8/14/1997. Covers 1700 workers in Okaloosa Co., FL
    - Item 3: Okaloosa County School Board and Okaloosa County Education Association, 1995-1996; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 8/14/1995 and expires on 8/14/1996. Covers an unknown number of workers in Okaloosa Co., FL
    - Item 4: Okaloosa County School Board and Okaloosa County Education Association, 1997-2000; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 8/14/1997 and expires on 8/14/2000. Covers 1700 workers in Okaloosa Co., FL
  - Code no.820833: Tulsa Public Schools and Tulsa Classroom Teachers Association, 1991-1993 (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Tulsa Board of Education and Tulsa Classroom Teachers Association, Inc., 1991-1992; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1991 and expires on 6/30/1992. Covers 2400 workers in Tulsa, OK
    - Item 2: Tulsa Board of Education and Tulsa Classroom Teachers Association, Inc., 1992-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1992 and expires on 8/31/1993. Covers 2300 workers in Tulsa, OK
  - Code no.820839: Nashville Board of Education and Nashville Education Association, 1995-1996 (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Metropolitan Nashville-Davidson County Board of Public Education and Metropolitan Nashville Education Association, 1995-1996; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1995 and expires on 6/30/1996. Covers 4500 workers in Nashville, TN
  - Code no.820843: Brevard County School Board and American Federation of Teachers, 1991-1995 (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Brevard County, Florida School Board and Brevard Federation of Teachers, Florida Education Association/United, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 2098, 1991-1992; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 8/18/1991 and expires on 8/19/1992. Covers 3000 workers in Brevard Co., FL
    - Item 2: Brevard County, Florida School Board and Brevard Federation of Teachers, Florida Education Association/United, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 2098, 1992-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 11/10/1992 and expires on 6/30/1993. Covers 3000 workers in Brevard Co., FL
    - Item 3: Brevard County, Florida, School Board and Brevard Federation of Teachers, Florida Education Association/United, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 2098, 1994-1995; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 8/16/1994 and expires on 6/30/1995. Covers 4000 workers in Brevard Co., FL
  - Code no.820844: Brevard County School Board and International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, 1991-1993 (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Brevard County, Florida School Board and International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, AFL-CIO, Local 1010, 1991-1992; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 9/10/1991 and expires on 6/30/1992. Covers 2300 workers in Brevard Co., FL
    - Item 2: Brevard County, Florida, School Board and International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, AFL-CIO, Local 1010, 1992-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 12/15/1992 and expires on 6/30/1993. Covers 2500 workers in Brevard Co., FL
  - Code no.830018: Wichita, Kansas Board of Education and Service Employees Union, 1980-1995 (Box 183, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Wichita, Kansas Unified School District 259 Board of Education and Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 513, 1980-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1980 and expires on 6/30/1982. Covers 1262 workers in Wichita, KS
    - Item 2: Wichita, Kansas Unified School District 259 Board of Education and Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 513, 1981-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1981 and expires on 6/30/1983. Covers 1150 workers in Wichita, KS
    - Item 3: Wichita, Kansas Unified School District 259 Board of Education and Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 513, 1983-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1983 and expires on 6/30/1985. Covers 1150 workers in Wichita, KS
    - Item 4: Wichita, Kansas Unified School District 259 Board of Education and Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 513, 1985-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1985 and expires on 6/30/1987. Covers an unknown number of workers in Wichita, KS
    - Item 5: Wichita, Kansas Unified School District 259 Board of Education and Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 513, 1987-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1987 and expires on 6/30/1989. Covers 1079 workers in Wichita, KS
    - Item 6: Wichita, Kansas Unified School District 259 Board of Education and Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 513, 1989-1991; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1989 and expires on 6/30/1991. Covers 1554 workers in Wichita, KS
    - Item 7: Wichita, Kansas Unified School District 259 Board of Education and Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 513 Addendum, 1989-1990; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1989 and expires on 6/30/1990. Covers an unknown number of workers in Wichita, KS
    - Item 8: Wichita, Kansas Unified School District 259 Board of Education and Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 513, 1992-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1992 and expires on 6/30/1994. Covers 1500 workers in Wichita, KS
    - Item 9: Wichita, Kansas Unified School District 259 Board of Education and Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 513, 1993-1995; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1993 and expires on 6/30/1995. Covers 1600 workers in Wichita, KS
  - Code no.830040: Cherry Creek School District #5 and National Education Association, 1996-2001 (Box 183, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Cherry Creek School District No. 5 and Cherry Creek Education Association, 1996-1997; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1996 and expires on 6/30/1997. Covers 2200 workers in Eaglewood, CO
    - Item 2: Cherry Creek School District No. 5 and Cherry Creek Education Association, 1997-1998; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1997 and expires on 6/30/1998. Covers 2200 workers in Eaglewood, CO
    - Item 3: Cherry Creek School District No. 5 and Cherry Creek Education Association, 1998-1999; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1998 and expires on 6/30/1999. Covers 2200 workers in Eaglewood, CO
    - Item 4: Cherry Creek School District No. 5 and Cherry Creek Education Association, 1999-2001; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1999 and expires on 6/30/2001. Covers 2200 workers in Eaglewood, CO
  - Code no.830095: Harford County Board of Education and Harford County Employees Association, 1983-1994 (Box 183, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Harford County Board of Education and Harford County Education Association, 1983-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1983 and expires on 6/30/1984. Covers 1600 workers in Harford Co., MD
    - Item 2: Harford County Board of Education and Harford County Education Association, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1986 and expires on 6/30/1989. Covers 1707 workers in Harford Co., MD
    - Item 3: Harford County Board of Education and Harford County Educational Services Council, 1989-1992; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1989 and expires on 6/30/1992. Covers an unknown number of workers in Harford Co., MD
    - Item 4: Harford County Board of Education and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1989-1992; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 15)
    - Item 5: Harford County Board of Education and Harford County Education Association, 1989-1992; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 15)
    - Item 6: Harford County Board of Education and Association of Public School Administrators and Supervisors or Harford County, 1989-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1989 and expires on 6/30/1994. Covers an unknown number of workers in Harford Co., MD
  - Code no.830182: Memphis City School and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1977-1995 (Box 183, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Memphis City Schools Board of Education and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Local 1773, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1977 and expires on 10/31/1980. Covers 1800 workers in Memphis, TN
    - Item 2: Memphis City Schools Board of Education and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Local 1773, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1980 and expires on 10/31/1983. Covers 1904 workers in Memphis, TN
    - Item 3: Memphis City Schools Board of Education and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Local 1773, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1983 and expires on 10/31/1986. Covers 1900 workers in Memphis, TN
    - Item 4: Memphis City Schools Board of Education and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Local 1773, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1986 and expires on 10/31/1989. Covers 1800 workers in Memphis, TN
    - Item 5: Memphis City Schools Board of Education and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Local 1773, 1992-1995; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1992 and expires on 10/31/1995. Covers 1700 workers in Memphis, TN
  - Code no.830204: Salt Lake City, Board of Education and Salt Lake Teachers Association, 1976-1996 (Box 183, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Salt Lake City Board of Education and Salt Lake Teachers Association Addendum, 1976-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1976 and expires on 6/30/1977. Covers an unknown number of workers in Salt Lake City, UT
    - Item 2: Salt Lake City Board of Education and Salt Lake Teachers Association, 1976-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1976 and expires on 6/30/1977. Covers 1225 workers in Salt Lake City, UT
    - Item 3: Salt Lake CityBoard of Education and Salt Lake Teachers Association, 1977-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1977 and expires on 6/30/1977. Covers 1200 workers in Salt Lake City, UT
    - Item 4: Salt Lake City Board of Education and Salt Lake Teachers Association, 1983-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1983 and expires on 6/30/1984. Covers 1200 workers in Salt Lake City, UT
    - Item 5: Salt Lake City Board of Education and Salt Lake Teachers Association, 1992-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1992 and expires on 6/1/1993. Covers 1300 workers in Salt Lake City, UT
    - Item 6: Salt Lake City School District Board of Education and Salt Lake Teachers Association, 1995-1996; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 8/30/1995 and expires on 6/30/1996. Covers an unknown number of workers in Salt Lake City, UT
  - Code no.830223: Chicago Board of education and Chicago Teachers Union, 1987-1995 (Box 183, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Chicago Board of Education and Chicago Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1, 1987-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1987 and expires on 8/31/1989. Covers 30000 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 2: Chicago Board of Education and Chicago Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1, 1989-1990; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1989 and expires on 8/31/1990. Covers 30000 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 3: Chicago Board of Education and Chicago Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1, 1990-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1990 and expires on 8/31/1993. Covers 30000 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 4: Chicago Board of Education and Chicago Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1 Addendum, 1991-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1991 and expires on 8/31/1993. Covers 30000 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 5: Chicago Board of Education and Chicago Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1, 1993-1995; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 183, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1993 and expires on 8/31/1995. Covers 30000 workers in New York, NY
  - Code no.830248: New York City School District and American Federation of Teachers, 1978-1984 (Box 184, Folder 1)